It has begun. Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series.
This is Haruna Sakamoto from Team Shachi.
And,
I'm Shinju Yoshise, wife of Ikunari and O-oku.
Pleased to meet you.
They're talking to each other.
I'm very excited.
Today, Pearl and Haru, we are going to have a dialogue,
Would you like to start by listing some of the things we have in common?
Yes, we do.
First of all, our color is green.
Yes, Haru is yellowish green, and Pearl is green, so we are a bit alike.
It's a color that is easy on the eyes. The opposite, yellowish green is good.
What? Is that so?
So they're the same.
It's almost the same?
But it was green when it was first announced in the spring.
Oh, really?
I was told it would be Tsubasaki green,
I wanted yellowish green, so I wrote a blog post saying I wanted tsubasaki green,
I said it's good. That's how it turned out. Is that so? But then I blogged about how good it was, and they said it was good.
Oh, yeah.
That's how it happened.
Really?
It's too late.
Too late?
As expected.
I'm feeling yellowish-green.
My feelings are yellowish green. That's about it,
The rest is hobbies and special skills, so we both write "dancing.
That's right.
You like it, don't you?
Yes, I do. It's strong.
Have you been dancing since you were little?
Yes, I have. Since I was a child.
I did all kinds of things.
That's why I don't have a specific one,So, this is what I mean,
Oh, I see. I can go to many genres.
I like.
I like it.
It's a little difficult when you can go to them.
I love dancing too.
That's one of the things we have in common,
So, with these commonalities, we have already decided on the theme of the first dialogue,
I have already decided on the theme of the first dialogue.
Yay!
I'm sure many of you are guessing what I'm going to say when you see this response,
Our theme for the dialogue is,
Seino!
Slam dunk!
These two seem to be in a bit of trouble.
They look like they're in trouble. You love Slam Dunk, don't you? I love it.
The reason I started liking it, too, is because I read it in the Corona Disaster,
I started reading manga after reading about the Corona disaster,
I started to like it because I thought it was interesting,
When did it all start?
My parents liked Slam Dunk,
They told me to read it.
They told me to read Slam Dunk.
So I read it when I was in elementary school.
I see. So you are by far the most senior person in terms of experience,
Time is not a factor this time.
It has nothing to do with it.
I'm glad.
The feeling of liking.
Today, as long as we have time together, I would like to shout that I love Slam Dunk.
It's good.
Yes, it is.
I just told you how it all started.
So you really mean you were in elementary school?
That's right.
I was hooked on Slam Dunk when I was in elementary school.
I wanted to be that slam dunk.I wanted to be that slam dunk.
When I was in elementary school.
I wanted to be?
I didn't want to be a character.
I wanted to be Slam Dunk.
Oh, that's great.
That's why I played basketball all the time, even during church vacations.
I see.
So you were in the basketball team?
Not at all.
We were in different clubs.
Yes, I was in the art club. I was in the art club.
That's right.
It's the opposite,
But I wanted to play basketball, and we called it the boys' club.
So that's how it was.
That's nice. You knew about it before that.
I wanted to know about it because, as I mentioned earlier, I saw it for the first time at the Corona Disaster,
I had never read many manga, shounen manga, in my life. Until now.
Is that so?
There were a few shoujo manga here and there,
I decided to start reading Corona Disaster for the first time,
I would like to read Oni no Kai for the first time.
After Oni no Kai.
I've been recommended to read Slum and others in that vein, so I thought I'd give it a try,
And I got the impression that it was easy to read all at once.
That was good, too.
It was good.
It's also good that it's a bit short.
Like you still want to see more.
Yeah, yeah.
I saw it and got hooked on it. I thought it was originally a basketball manga,
It's really a human drama,
Yes, that's right. That's right.
That's right.
The characters are great.
There are so many characters.
Characters with great personalities,Characters with insanely good personalities,
May I say that I am a guesser among them?
I will say so.
My guess is Shinji Michishigehisa.
What's wrong?
It's already "Shinji Michishigehisa.
I like Shinji Michishigehisa.
He is passionate.
I really like his humanity,
Everyone experiences a setback at least once in their lives. In the course of human life. So, after his setback, he decided that he wanted to come back,
So you want to come back and play basketball again,
Also, basketball players are also very passionate, aren't they?
I was really drawn to it,
I was really attracted to it,
And I like the quotes more than anything else.
There are a lot of them, aren't there?
Yes, there are. There are a lot of quotes that make me feel like I'm drunk,
That's what I like about him.
It's good, isn't it?
I like it.
It's because of the way I like them.
When you say quotes like that, if it's reasonable, I understand.
It makes you want to cheer them on.
It's good. It's full of love.
Which character do you like best?
There are so many, but you have to narrow it down to one.
Yes, that's right. Just one.
It's so hard to decide,
Yohei Mito.
That's how you feel?
I really like that. That's how I feel.
I like it a lot.
I know many of you may be surprised to see me suddenly coming from a place other than the busky stalwarts,
It was because there was a person who understood and supported him the most among Sakuragi's friends in the "Sakuragi group," a group of delinquents,
Sakurai, the main character,
Sakurai, the main character, was able to concentrate on basketball,
He is an amateur and there are a lot of people around him,
He was afraid many times, but he kept a straight attitude, right?How many times were they afraid to go straight, but they went straight for it?
There were various scenes with fights and so on.
That's right. Mitsui.
That's right.
Mitsui came. That's the theory.
Thanks. I went to tell Mitsui, too. You don't know. That's right. Mitsui came to me. Thanks for that theory.
Thank you. Mitsui came.
You don't know that. I really don't.
I really like that attitude.
She's the kind of girl who supports you because she thinks you're sweet.
I feel like she has her friends first.
I like Mitsui.
I understand. I understand.
That's what I've experienced so far,
I mean, you were always at the top of your game, even with Lucao,
But he is many things, isn't he?
I like his humanity,
Mitsui is also the best in terms of visuals.
Face?
His face.
I'm sorry for the suddenness of the question.
I think there are many categories. When choosing the best, you have to be very selective. There's one in the visual category. I think there are many categories.
When you select the finalists.
Yes, I do.
There is one in the visual category.
What? What do you mean?
You know, of course I like his visual name,
He's pretty good looking.
I mean, he's good-looking,
Fujima is at the top of the visual name list.
Here it comes. There it is.
There it is.
Yes, he is.
It's cool.
I like Fujima a lot, and it's really cool that he's like a sparkling idol,
I was more squeamish than when Fujima came out,
It's kind of cool there.It's a little bit cool there.
So that's the kind of visual.
Coming from a different angle.
But it's still Michishige.
So, it's all about the total.
Isn't it cool?
It's cool.
Among Michishige, there are all kinds of Michishige. Even the hairstyle.
I like the junior high school Michishige, but I think the current Michishige is the best,
I like the junior high school Michishige, but I think the current Michishige is the best.
She looks good.
Dong hair, center pad, and so on.
Thank you for showing us all the different hairstyles.
You're right.
I don't get it when he does his hair in different ways and plays around with it.
But it's cool.
It's good looking.
What's with the fresh look?
It's not fair.
It's cool. Also, it's strong. The freshness stands out because there are members who are pretty naughty.
Yes, that cap.
That's right. That's right. That's right.
It's nice, isn't it?
I recommend it.
I recommend them.
Do you have a favorite scene?
What about this game? I don't know.
I think the three brain games are the best.
Mitsui himself shines so brightly,
He played such an active role in the battle of the three brains that I think we would not have won if it were not for him,
And, more than anything else, there were a lot of English words.
He speaks a lot of English.
That's right.
I saw the movie "The Last Airbender",
I saw it. I want to see it with you.
Let's go see it.
I read the manga one more week for the movie too.I read another week of comics for the movie as well.
It's really great.
Thank you for letting me help you.
That's right.
It was cool to see that movie and still think it was cool.
Micchan from Northen.
He was so exhausted, but he made a decision while saying that he couldn't even lift his arm for me.
Ahhh...
I knew it,
I thought, "It's really Michiichan,
He started to make the decision for me.
That's what I like about him.
Ocell is really cool.
He was really good looking, that's for sure. The Sanno match.
But in terms of a match, yes.
I think it's a Sanno fight,
There are a lot of them. There are a lot of them.
That's right. I said, "They're all good, so you have to narrow it down to one.
Like the one I gave the second prize for stamina, because the other characters are great, too,
That's right.
Odane-kun is good too.
Odane-kun, right.
Your guy is cool, too,
And the rest,
The guy in the red taping.
That's taping, for God's sake.
That's right.
That guy over there got me, too.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it? Golly.
Golly is good.
It's good.
After all, if it weren't for Golly.
It might be hard to have a basketball team in the first place.
That's for sure.
The body is good, isn't it?
I've told you about all the characters in Slam Dunk,I've told you about all the characters in Slam Dunk,
There is a diagnostic tool called "Slam Dunk Diagnosis" that can help you determine which character you are closest to,
Have you ever tried it?
I have not.
Would you like to try it now?
Yes!
I definitely want Mitsui. Mitsui! I definitely want Mitsui.
I definitely want Mitsui.
The Slam Dunks Jury
Okay, the slam dunks jury is ready.
Yes!
Then, let's do it together.
Start!
Then let's do it together. Start!
Here we go.
Are you with me?
I'll say we're together, and that's all I can say.
I'm with you.
Okay, I'll just go to Miyoshi for a minute.
Here's what our diagnosis came up with.
Seino!
Sakuragi!
Wow!
I did it!
That's great!
Wow! It was Sakuragi!
They are a golden duo, aren't they?
They're the best combination ever!
Hey, hot!
Sakuragi is the best of the two.
Yay!You did it!
You did it! That's great!
What's your personality like? Will something like that come up?
Yes, it does. Read a little there.
Your personality is very simple and you often do things for others.
I see.
When you are similar to Sacramento, the similarities are...
I wonder if that's right.
Ah, but everything is at your own pace.
Ah...
It says here that he's easygoing, simple, honest, and carbonated.
Is that a compliment?
Is that a compliment? This one.
Luka was very surprised,
But I can feel it.
You feel it?
I think he's very fast-paced.
Luka doesn't show a cool expression,
But I can tell that he is very fast-paced.
Sometimes when I watch him, I feel it. He doesn't show it, but it's really nice, so you might be able to tell.
Please take a look at him.
Please calm down and join us in the country where you feel like you're in the middle of the world.
Scene
I still want to support you.
Hm...
As a fellow slam dunk, I hope we can continue to be friends. I'm really glad to meet you.
Cyber-i. Please take care of me.
It was great.
Let's go see the movie. Together.
Let's go.
Let's talk. Time now because it's not enough again.
Yes, it is.
I hope the time will come when we will get to know each other better and I will be able to bring you our even deeper love, so please do.
Tomorrow, I would like to challenge you both to a game.
Looking forward to it. Look forward to it as well.
My partner so far is with Haruna Sakamoto of Team Shachi,So far, the partners were Haruna Sakamoto of Team Shachi and,
Ehinari and Mr. Oki's Masatsugu Yoshida.
See you tomorrow!